artsmia.org 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy and Website Info –– Minneapolis Institute of Art

### Privacy Statement

Minneapolis Institute of Art (“Mia,” “we, “us” or “our”) respects the personal information you provide to us. This Privacy Statement explains how we use, share and protect the personal information we collect in connection with your use of this website (“Site”). By using the Site, you consent to our use of the Information (as defined below) we collect, as further described below.

#### The Information we Collect: PII and NPI

We only collect personally-identifiable information (“PII”) that you provide to us. PII includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, and phone number.

We collect non-personal information (“NPI”) during your use of the Site. This type of information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. NPI includes, but is not limited to: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring websites. NPI is used for the operation of the Site, to maintain quality of our products and services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Site.

#### Use of Your Information

PII is used by Mia to provide you with information about Mia activities. This includes our programs, membership, marketing and development opportunities, products and special events that we believe might be of interest to you. We also use your PII to recognize and show appreciation for your participation with and contributions to Mia. We will disclose your PII, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend our rights or property or to protect the personal safety of our other users or that of the public.

We may keep track of Site pages you visit through cookies (as further explained below). The data we collect is used to deliver customized content. We may also use PII to contact you with requests to participate in surveys.

We may share information we collect with third parties to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for product deliveries. Except as provided in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, rent or lease PII to third parties.

#### Cookies

We use cookies, and other website use-tracking technologies (collectively, “cookies”) to provide you with an enhanced user-experience. We do not track your activity outside of the Site. Please note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking technologies on your web browser may also disable some functionality of the Site. You should consult your web browser settings to determine which cookie options are available.

#### Links to Third Party Sites and Services

The Site may provide links to third party websites. These websites are not covered by this Privacy Statement. These links are provided solely for your convenience. We do not review these third party websites and we assume no liability arising from your use of them.

Client uses Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather End User’s data from financial institutions. By using our service, you grant Client and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal).

#### Security

We strive to maintain reasonable security measures designed to safeguard the PII collected. However, no security measures are invulnerable to attack, and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your PII. We are not responsible for the security of PII you transmit to the Site over networks that we do not control, including, but not limited to, the Internet and wireless networks.

#### Correction and Contacting Us

You may be able to request correction of PII that we have under our control. To do so, you may contact us at [admin@artsmia.org](mailto:admin@artsmia.org).

Your right to correct your PII is subject to applicable legal restrictions and the availability of the PII. We may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting making corrections.

If you wish to make inquiries or complaints or have other concerns about our Information collection and use practices, you may write to us using the contact information above.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

You may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from us by clicking on the Unsubscribe link or by emailing us to the email listed above.

#### Children Under Thirteen

The Site is intended to be accessible and enjoyed by general audiences. We do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of thirteen.

If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this Site. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of thirteen, and have reason to believe your child has accessed the Site and provided PII, you may contact us using the contact information above.

#### Privacy Statement Changes

This Privacy Statement may be revised from time to time. If we intend to use or disclose PII for purposes materially different than those described in this Privacy Statement, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you. Your use of our Site following any changes to this Privacy Statement constitutes your acceptance of any such changes.

_Last revised on August 9, 2017._

#### This website uses Google AdWords.

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Minneapolis Institute of Art website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely using [cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or permanently by using a [browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).

#### Font Icons

This website makes use of font icons by the following publishers:

**Font Awesome**

Copyright © 2012 by Dave Gandy

Author: Dave Gandy  
License: SIL ()  
Homepage: <http://fortawesome.github.com/Font-Awesome/>

**Web Symbols**

Copyright © 2011 by Just Be Nice studio. All rights reserved.

Author: Just Be Nice studio  
License: SIL (<http://scripts.sil.org/OFL>)  
Homepage: <http://www.justbenicestudio.com/>

**Entypo**

Copyright © 2012 by Daniel Bruce

Author: Daniel Bruce  
License: CC BY-SA (<http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/>)  
Homepage: [http://www.entypo.com](http://www.entypo.com/)

**Modern Pictograms**

Copyright © 2012 by John Caserta. All rights reserved.

Author: John Caserta  
License: SIL (<http://scripts.sil.org/OFL>)  
Homepage: <http://thedesignoffice.org/project/modern-pictograms/>

**Zocial**

Copyright © 2012 by Sam Collins

Author: Sam Collins  
License: MIT (<http://opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php>)  
Homepage: <http://zocial.smcllns.com/>
